theconstructsim.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy | The Construct

**Effective May 25, 2018**

**The Construct takes data privacy seriously. This privacy policy explains who we are, how we collect, share and use Personal Information, and how you can exercise your privacy rights.** ** **

**We recommend that you read this privacy policy in full to ensure you are fully informed.**

**If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your Personal Information, you can contact us directly at**[ **info@theconstructsim.com**](mailto:info@theconstructsim.com) **.**

## **How We Collect and Use Information**

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service.   
We collect the following types of information about you:

### **INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU DIRECTLY**

  * **Account information** : You can browse our site without providing personal information, but you must register in order to access most of the features of Service. We ask for certain information such as your username, email address and password when you create a        Robot Ignite Academy or ROS Development Studio account, or if you correspond with us.
  * **Messages and User Content** : We may retain any messages you send through the Service, and may collect information you provide in User Content you post to the Service.
  * **Third-party email operator** : we may collect your information through third-party email marketing service operator (e.g. Mailchimp) For more information, please read their [Privacy Policy and Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages. We may also send you Service-related emails (e.g. account verification, marketing email, change or updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices).

### **INFORMATION WE MAY RECEIVE FROM SOCIAL NETWORKING SITES**

If you create an account on our website through a third-party connection or log-in, for example through Facebook or Google, that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to The Construct. This information could include the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. If you allow us access to your friends list, your friends’ user IDs, and your connection to those friends, may be used and stored to make your experience more social, and to allow you to invite your friends to use our Service as well as provide you with updates if and when your friends join The Construct. The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the social network. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the The Construct Service.

### **INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED**

We automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our website or use our Service. When you visit the Site, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g. the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. We may collect log file information from your browser or mobile device each time you access the Service. Log file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service. We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Service.

We use or may use the data collected through cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on our website and our Service; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; and (f) otherwise to plan for and enhance our service. We may associate information we automatically collect with your other information.

for you which containing the following:  
–  How to build a gazebo differential drive robot  
–  How to add a controlled arm to that robot  
–  How to build a simulated environment for that robot  
–  and how to add a plugin for Gazebo

  1. ## IDENTIFYING DATA

In compliance with the information duty established under article 10 of the 34/2002 Law dated 11th July from the Society Information Services and Electronic Trade of Spain (Servicios de la Sociedad de la Información y del Comercio Electrónico) the following data is hereby. stated: the company owning web domain is **THE CONSTRUCT SIM, S.L** (hereafter **THE CONSTRUCT** ), with address on **Avenida de les Corts Catalanes, number 608, 3º-D,   Barcelona (08007)**, **SPAIN** C.I.F. number: **B66615543** registered at the B-474075, 45007, 29. Contact email address: [info@theconstructsim.com](mailto:info@theconstructsim.com) from the website.

  2. ## USERS

The access and/or use of online platform **THE CONSTRUCT** attributes the condition of USER, to whom accepts from such access or use, the General Conditions of Use hereby stated.  The established Conditions will be applied regardless of the Contracting General Conditions which, in such case, result in obligatory compliance.

  3. ## USE OF THE ONLINE PORTAL

[www.theconstructsim.com](http://www.theconstructsim.com/) gives access to a variety of information, services, programs or data (hereafter “content”) on Internet belonging to **THE CONSTRUCT** or to the licenses the USERS might have access to.  THE USER assumes responsibility of the use of the online portal.  Such responsibility extends to the necessary registration to access specific services or content.

In such registration, the USER will be responsible for providing truthful and legal information.  As a consequence of this registration, the USER could be provided with a password. The USER will be responsible for the password and will be committed to make confidential and diligent use of it.  The USER commits to making good use of the content and services (for example chat services, discussion forums or groups) that **THE CONSTRUCT** offers through its online portal and with notifying character and in no case limiting to not use them to (i) incur in illicit or illegal activities or against good faith and public order; (ii) spread propaganda with racist, xenophobic, pornographic-illegal, advocacy of terrorism or any attempt towards human rights violations content: (iii) cause damage to the physical and logical systems of **THE CONSTRUCT** , its providers or third parties, introduce or spread viruses in the net or any other physical or logical systems which are susceptible to causing the aforementioned damage; (iv) attempt to access or in its case, use other users’ email accounts or modify or manipulate their messages.  **THE CONSTRUCT** reserves the right to remove all those comments or contributions which affect another person’s dignity, which are discriminatory, xenophobic, racist, pornographic, attempt against childhood or youth, order or public safety or which are not appropriate for publication.  In any case, **THE CONSTRUCT** will not be responsible for the USERS opinions through forums, chats or other participation tools.

  4. ## DATA PROTECTION

**THE CONSTRUCT** follows the guidelines of Organic Law 15/1999 from 13th December of Personal Data Protection, the Real Edict 1720/2007 of 21st December by which the Development Regulation of the Organic Law is approved as well as other existing regulation and ensures the correct use and processing of the users’ personal data.  For this, along with each personal registration form, in the services that the user might request from **THE CONSTRUCT** , will advice the user of the existence and acceptance of the conditions and processing of data in each case, informing of the responsibility of the file created, the responsible address, the possibility to enforce its access rights, amendment, cancellation or opposition, the purpose of the procedure and the communication of data to third parties.

Additionally, **THE CONSTRUCT** informs that it fulfills Law 34/2002 from 11th July of the Society Information Services and Electronic Trade of Spain (Servicios de la Sociedad de la Información y del Comercio Electrónico) and will request its consent to the processing of its email with commercial purposes only.

  5. ## INTELLECTUAL AND INDUSTRIAL PROPERTY

**THE CONSTRUCT** by itself or as an assignee, is the intellectual and industrial property right holder of its web page as well as the elements within the page (including images, sound, audio, video, software or texts; brands, logos, color combination, structure, design, selection of used material, necessary computer programs, access, use etc), assignee of **THE CONSTRUCT** or its licensors.

All the rights reserved. In accordance with articles 8 and 32.1, second paragraph, from the Intellectual Property Law of Spain, the reproduction, distribution and public communication including its disposition form, of the totality or part of the contents of this web page, with commercial means, under any support and through any technical method are strictly prohibited without the authorization of the **THE CONSTRUCT**. The USER is committed to respect the rights of the Intellectual and Industrial Property owned by **THE CONSTRUCT**. The USER could visualize the elements of the web portal and even print, copy or save them in their computer hard drive or in any other physical support as long as it is solely for personal and private use. The USER must abstain from removing, changing, avoiding or manipulating any protection device or security system that may be installed in the **THE CONSTRUCT** pages.

  6. ## SUSPENSION OF WARRANTY AND RESPONSIBILITY

**THE CONSTRUCT** is not responsible, under any circumstances, of the damages and losses of any kind that could cause including but not limited to: mistakes or omissions in the contents, lack of availability of the web portal or the transfer of virus or malicious or wrongful programs in spite of having adopted all the necessary strategies to prevent it.

  7. ## MODIFICATIONS

**THE CONSTRUCT** reserves the right to undergo any modification to the web portal, which might be necessary, without previous notice, being able to change, delete or add content or services given through the page as well as the way these are presented or located in the web portal.

  8. ## LINKS

In the case that in [www.theconstructsim.com](http://www.theconstructsim.com/) there were links or hyperlinks to other internet sites, **THE CONSTRUCT** will not exert any type of control over such sites and their contents.  In no case will **THE CONSTRUCT** assume any responsibility for the contents of a link belonging to an external web site, nor will it guarantee the technical availability, quality, credibility, accuracy, validity and constitutionality of any material or information contained in any of such links and hyperlinks or other internet sites.

Equally, the inclusion of these external links will not imply any type of association, merge or participation with those entities.

  9. ##  EXCLUSIONARY RIGHT

**THE CONSTRUCT** reserves the right to refuse or withdraw the access to the portal and/or its offered services without previous notice, personally or through a third party, to those users who breach the present General Use Conditions.

  10. ## GENERALITIES

**THE CONSTRUCT** will pursue any breach of the present conditions as well as any inappropriate use of the web portal applying all the civil and criminal actions which, by right, may belong to it.

  11. ## MODIFICATION AND DURATION OF THE PRESENT CONDITIONS

**THE CONSTRUCT** may modify at any moment the conditions hereby established, being properly published as they appear.

The validity of the forementioned conditions will go in accordance to their exposure and will continue to be effective until duly published or until replaced for other.

  12. ## APPLICABLE LEGISLATION AND JURISDICTION

The relationship between **THE CONSTRUCT** and the USER, will operate under the current Spanish rule and any controversy will be submitted to courts in the city of **BARCELONA.**

##
